PRIVACY POLICY
==============

ShoptoCook, LLC (the "Company") is committed to maintaining robust privacy protections for its users. Our Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Service.

For purposes of this Agreement, "Service" refers to the Company's service which can be accessed via our website at www.shoptocook.com. The terms "we," "us," and "our" refer to the Company. "You" refers to you, as a user of Service. By accepting our Privacy Policy you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT
-------------------------

We may collect the following information:

* name
* contact information including email address
* demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
* payment information to complete an online transaction
* other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

II. HOW WE USE AND SHARE INFORMATION
------------------------------------

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise share for marketing purposes your information with third parties without your consent. We do share your information with vendors who are performing services for the Company, such as the servers for our email communications who are provided access to user's email address for purposes of sending emails from us. Those vendors use your information only at our direction and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

In general, the information you provide to us is used to help us communicate with you. For example, we use information to contact users in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, provide technical support, and inform users about promotional offers.

_Cookies_

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

_Business Transaction_

In the event we undergo a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of our assets may continue to process your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at any time in the future, we will post the policy changes to the Site so that you may opt out of the new information practices. We suggest that you check the Site periodically if you are concerned about how your information is used.

III. HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION
-------------------------------

We implement security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. Your account is protected by your account password and we urge you to take steps to keep your information safe by not disclosing your password and by logging out of your account after each use. We further protect your information from potential security breaches by implementing certain technological security measures including encryption, firewalls and secure socket layer technology. However, these measures do not guarantee that your information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. By using our Service, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

IV. YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------------

You have the right at any time to prevent us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When we send a promotional communication to a user, the user can opt out of further promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each promotional e-mail. Please note that notwithstanding the promotional preferences you indicate by either unsubscribing or opting out in the Settings section of the Site, we may continue to send you administrative emails including, for example, periodic updates to our Privacy Policy.

V. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
--------------------------

As part of the Service, we may provide links to or compatibility with other websites or applications. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites or the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and the Service. Therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third party website accessed by selecting a link on our Site or via our Service. To the extent that you access or use the Service through or on another website or application, then the privacy policy of that other website or application will apply to your access or use of that site or application. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them.

VI. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
---------------------------------

The Company reserves the right to change this policy and our Terms of Service at any time. You should periodically check the Site and this privacy page for updates.

VII. CONTACT US
---------------

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us by sending an email to inquire@shoptocook.com.

Last Updated: This Privacy Policy was last updated on 11/22/2016
